[{"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a225", "question": "In 1997, who released the hit song entitled \"I'll Be Missing You\"?", "answer": "Puff Daddy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cf6", "question": "What did Becky Thatcher's father do for a living in \"The Adventures of Tom Sawyer\"?", "answer": "He was a judge", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea77aaff048f679a45abcc", "question": "What is the more common term for odontalgia?", "answer": "Toothache", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339962", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what nickname did Milhouse give himself?", "answer": "Thrillhouse", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d3f", "question": "What TV show, besides \"Green Acres\", is set in the town of Hooterville?", "answer": "Petticoat Junction", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea3fa7ff048f679a45ab61", "question": "How many stomachs does a llama have?", "answer": "Three", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe9f034ff048f679a45aa99", "question": "Phobophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Phobias", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a453", "question": "Due to its shape, which European country refers to itself as The Hexagon?", "answer": "France", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a402", "question": "Which city has the world's largest castle complex?", "answer": "Prague, Czech Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1a2", "question": "What is Ozzy Osbourne's real first name?", "answer": "John", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaa5", "question": "Minsk is the capital of which European country?", "answer": "Belarus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fecd44fec223966ae8f88cb", "question": "How many people does John Wick kill in the film \"John Wick\"?", "answer": "77", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133abf4", "question": "What state capital city lies on the River Torrens?", "answer": "Adelaide", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390ff", "question": "Who is the Roman equivalent of the Greek goddess Aphrodite?", "answer": "Venus", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "591c35f7815febcc896f9262", "question": "What firm made the B25 Micro Computer?", "answer": "Burroughs", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59774433284458f1d785442e", "question": "The original name of New York City was what?", "answer": "New Amsterdam", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeea", "question": "In which war was the \"Battle of Ramillies\"?", "answer": "War of Spanish Succession", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c565", "question": "How many toes does a pig have on each foot?", "answer": "4", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f6f", "question": "What vehicle was driven by Arnie Cunningham?", "answer": "Christine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "601b4c3b49076251badbead0", "question": "Which First Lady was the first to graduate college?", "answer": "Lucy Hayes -- The wife of President Rutherford B. Hayes, she received her degree from Wesleyan Female College at the age of 18.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c4dc877e98cb977789a8", "question": "Which US state's motto is \"Live free or die\"?", "answer": "New Hampshire", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133936a", "question": "What was Indiana Jones' dad afraid of in the movie \"Indiana Jones and The Last Crusade\"?", "answer": "Rats", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab96a986faa38a764be521", "question": "Despite not being the first company to make a minivan, which company introduced the first successful mass-produced minivan in 1983?", "answer": "Chrysler", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea82a5ff048f679a45ac22", "question": "Where is human skin thinnest?", "answer": "Eyelids", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febd9937e83c707845b217b", "question": "What is the name of the woman Mario is attempting to save from the giant ape in the original Donkey Kong?", "answer": "Pauline", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389eb", "question": "What major comedy star played Garp in the movie adaptation of John Irvning's \"The World According to Garp\"?", "answer": "Robin Williams", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a04d", "question": "Which director was responsible for four of the highest grossing films of the 1980s?", "answer": "Steven Spielberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "60062b98c9d816e292245c20", "question": "Where is the first underwater art museum in the U.S.?", "answer": "Santa Rosa Beach, Florida", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fecc2dcec223966ae8f8878", "question": "What comedy became the first film directed by a woman to gross over $100 million at the US box office?", "answer": "\"Big\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c52b", "question": "How many muscles are there in an elephant's trunk?", "answer": "40,000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133918b", "question": "Who was the first actress to appear on a postage stamp?", "answer": "Grace Kelly", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a953", "question": "What is the only US state with four consecutive consonants uninterrupted by spaces?", "answer": "New Hampshire", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c407", "question": "Who is typically credited with inventing the first DC motor in 1837?", "answer": "Thomas Davenport", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a1b", "question": "What fictional detective is often depicted smoking a pipe while wearing a deerstalker hat?", "answer": "Sherlock Holmes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5902a1a5cad1ec93f27df778", "question": "In English-speaking countries, what is Rauchbier typically referred to as?", "answer": "Smoked beer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113389f5", "question": "Which Paul McCartney and Wings album includes \"Picasso's Last Words\"?", "answer": "Band on the Run", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2ac", "question": "Which country invented the Wankel engine, also known as a rotary engine?", "answer": "Germany", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae66", "question": "Who was the first woman to be appointed a US Supreme Court Justice?", "answer": "Sandra Day O'Connor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fca", "question": "Which Canadian province is the setting for the novel \"Anne of Green Gables\"?", "answer": "Prince Edward Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fdd5ff70499cffc60b84237", "question": "Apart from the toga, what was the main article of Roman fashion?", "answer": "Tunic", "category": "history"}, {"id": "594a61902ebb971c1417fb88", "question": "How many hurdles are there in a 400 metres hurdle race?", "answer": "Ten", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd96bab23c87fd04dd15e1d", "question": "What's the most common first name among the First Ladies of the United States?", "answer": "Elizabeth", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c49b", "question": "Bubble wrap was invented accidentally by researchers who were trying to develop a new type of what?", "answer": "A 3-dimensional wallpaper", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a495", "question": "Which Australian state borders all other mainland states?", "answer": "South Australia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590723043745b36be7303a04", "question": "Who directed the 2003 film \"Love Actually\"?", "answer": "Richard Curtis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b34b", "question": "Which Cambodian party was Pol Pot the leader of?", "answer": "Khmer Rouge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffb67ef5dad637d903c8840", "question": "Kersti Kaljulaid was 46 years old when she became the youngest president ever elected to lead which country?", "answer": "Estonia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339666", "question": "In the TV show \"The Simpsons\", what is the name of Springfield's newspaper?", "answer": "The Springfield Shopper", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d057b1a1c922dd1ac64a2", "question": "What is Ronald Biggs famous for?", "answer": "Being one of the \"Great Train Robbers\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339934", "question": "What US city is mentioned in the first line of the Bob Seger song \"Turn the Page\"?", "answer": "Omaha", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c280", "question": "What abbreviation comes from libra, meaning pound in Latin?", "answer": "lb", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b492", "question": "Which country were the 1896 Olympic Games held in?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c220", "question": "When did \"Macho Man\" Randy Savage die?", "answer": "2011", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fc8560fabc30a8194e188af", "question": "In which three films did Bill Paxton and Michael Bien both have roles?", "answer": "\"Terminator\", \"Aliens\" and \"Tombstone\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b504", "question": "What are A.C. Milan, Ajax and Real Madrid?", "answer": "Soccer clubs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa12", "question": "What city is Sugarloaf Mountain located in?", "answer": "Rio de Janeiro", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fed2c08ec223966ae8f8915", "question": "What Vin Diesel film did David Twohy direct?", "answer": "\"The Chronicles Of Riddick\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a89e", "question": "What islands are home to most of the world's blue-footed boobies?", "answer": "The Galapagos Islands", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe7cb1d877e98cb97778a14", "question": "Trinidad and Tobago are a part of which continent?", "answer": "North America", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa83", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Colorado?", "answer": "Denver", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdeb", "question": "What Burlingame, California, company was founded in 1984 to provide blood and urine analysis to athletes?", "answer": "BALCO", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e6b5f9fb6c85e9e634ff46", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed \"Land of 10,000 Lakes\"?", "answer": "Minnesota", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e4", "question": "When was actor W. C. Fields born?", "answer": "1880", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c978", "question": "What mineral is also referred to as \"Fool's gold\"?", "answer": "Pyrite", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1c0", "question": "What army was founded by \"General\" William Booth?", "answer": "The Salvation Army", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ab1b3234fda37788a9a1dc0", "question": "What is the basis for guacamole?", "answer": "Avocado", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fad", "question": "What movie's title mission is completed using the Five-Point-Palm Exploding Heart Technique?", "answer": "Kill Bill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2a5", "question": "What nation was led by Peter the Great?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8f08401dd7bf43be5e7fd", "question": "How did pound cake get its name?", "answer": "Having one pound of each main ingredient", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe8f81f01dd7bf43be5e840", "question": "Achluophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Darkness", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339692", "question": "Who replaced Michael Keaton as Batman in the movie series by the same name?", "answer": "Val Kilmer", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6002446e4be4723ccac221a3", "question": "What Salt Lake City-born cartoonist produced classic portrayals of the era of the flapper, bootlegging, and jazz?", "answer": "One of the best known magazine illustrators of the 1920s, John Held Jr. was an American cartoonist, printmaker, and illustrator.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe76ba9eec85e375820b2c6", "question": "Which ski resort is known as the \"The Queen of the Dolomites\"?", "answer": "Cortina, Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59636abd967692ea8518999f", "question": "Which two cross-border neighbouring cities jointly celebrate July 1 and July 4 holidays with the International Freedom Festival?", "answer": "Windsor and Detroit", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a99", "question": "What other animal cartoon character made his screen debut as Porky Pig's nemesis in the 1937 short \"Porky's Duck Hunt\"?", "answer": "Daffy Duck", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393db", "question": "What actor played the role of Ichabod Crane in the 1999 movie \"Sleepy Hollow\"?", "answer": "Johnny Depp", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1a8", "question": "What is a coronet?", "answer": "A small, or simple crown", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59a1a29812f2a7826b9b871e", "question": "What was the name of the first synthetic plastic ever developed?", "answer": "Bakelite", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339531", "question": "What show debuted in 1963 and became the longest running sci-fi series?", "answer": "Doctor Who", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a200", "question": "Who was the very first actor to win two consecutive Best Actor Oscars?", "answer": "Spencer Tracy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd52", "question": "The Juno Award is an award given in what field?", "answer": "Canadian music", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fedd9e96ce05a3942286d7e", "question": "What was the name of the girl in the film \"Jurassic Park\"?", "answer": "Lex Murphy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59071bde3745b36be73039c5", "question": "Who is Tony Chu\u2019s partner in the comic series \"Chew\"?", "answer": "John Colby", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb5b835dad637d903c881b", "question": "What is the most-popular meat served on Christmas in the United Kingdom?", "answer": "Turkey meat", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339449", "question": "How much are the guns worth in the 1998 movie \"Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels\"?", "answer": "$250,000", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0e3", "question": "How old was the Elephant Man when he died?", "answer": "27", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b201", "question": "What ship was commanded by William Bligh?", "answer": "Bounty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d84", "question": "What time-travel film was shot on Michigan's three-mile-long Mackinac Island?", "answer": "Somewhere in Time", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca4c", "question": "What would be scored by the Apgar score?", "answer": "Health of newborns", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397b6", "question": "Who became \"king of the cowboys\" when Gene Autry entered the army in WWII?", "answer": "Roy Rogers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c8f2fbde8045e48466e4", "question": "Which farm animal is known as a ram, ewe, and lamb?", "answer": "Sheep -- Female sheep are called ewes, male sheep are called rams, and baby sheep are called lambs.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393c5", "question": "Who played the role of Sarah in the movie \"The Terminator\"?", "answer": "Linda Hamilton", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8b0", "question": "Miranda orbits what planet of the solar system?", "answer": "Uranus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c261", "question": "How many kilograms are there in a short ton?", "answer": "907", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a854", "question": "Machu Picchu is also known as what?", "answer": "Lost City of the Incas", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ae", "question": "How many bits are there in a byte?", "answer": "8", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb2d", "question": "Someone who raises false alarms is said to cry what?", "answer": "Wolf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a43d", "question": "Where do people traditionally dance the flamenco?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59e6b2fffb6c85e9e634ff41", "question": "Despite being released at the end of 1998, who had a  #1 hit in 1999 with the song \"Fly Away\"?", "answer": "Lenny Kravitz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fde519ec6c6b019850c9a90", "question": "Herbert Hoover became well known when he organized relief efforts for what country after World War I?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fd6a1826c0f9723ab15cb3a", "question": "Who was the first honorary citizen of the U.S.?", "answer": "Winston Churchill", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be82", "question": "What raconteur and Topkapi star joked that he wanted his tombstone to read \"Keep off the grass\"?", "answer": "Peter Ustinov", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015ddd1fe83fe1f2a824b64", "question": "Who invented the color wheel?", "answer": "Sir Isaac Newton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58bb342be368446ca7bd684a", "question": "What year was the instant coffee, Nescafe, released onto the market?", "answer": "1938", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6e5", "question": "What sport has its name abbreviated to BMX?", "answer": "Bicycle Moto-cross", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58d1193d4fea7fe947a2228c", "question": "Which song from the \"White Album\" was originally titled \"Maharishi\"?", "answer": "Sexy Sadie", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133982c", "question": "What town was the setting of The Andy Griffith Show?", "answer": "Mayberry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bcd", "question": "What is the supposed site of the Isle of Avalon?", "answer": "Glastonbury", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339110", "question": "In which play by Tennessee Williams would you encounter the character \"Big Daddy\"?", "answer": "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9f5", "question": "Which bird is the national bird of Iceland?", "answer": "Gyrfalcon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60121ab563c99d48cd169b06", "question": "What were clocks missing before 1577?", "answer": "Minute hands", "category": "general"}, {"id": "593c4a30b8198b9a2b07795a", "question": "What is the name of Atticus Finch's daughter in the film \"To Kill a Mockingbird\"?", "answer": "Scout", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c351", "question": "Which two scientists first proposed that DNA is structured in a double helix?", "answer": "James D. Watson and Francis Crick", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac4e", "question": "What was the code name for the development of the A-bomb?", "answer": "The Manhattan Project", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c778", "question": "What animal species were depicted as evil characters in \"The Wonderful Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer": "Monkeys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5b4", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Evergreen State\"?", "answer": "Washington", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "58ab1782baab681b09292183", "question": "What numbers appear on Donald Duck\u2019s car plate?", "answer": "313", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b33e", "question": "Archbishop Makarios of Cyprus was exiled in 1956 to where?", "answer": "The Seychelles", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7bec1877e98cb97778963", "question": "What is the fastest flowing river in the world?", "answer": "Amazon", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015dfa4fe83fe1f2a824b7c", "question": "What queen defeated and killed Cyrus the Great of Persia?", "answer": "Tomyris", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a260", "question": "What British group had a hit with the song \"The House of the Rising Sun\" in 1964?", "answer": "The Animals", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389bf", "question": "What did Hannibal Lecter say French people taste like?", "answer": "Chicken", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a364", "question": "Where is Mount Olympus?", "answer": "Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c439", "question": "Agoraphobia is the irrational fear of what?", "answer": "Places and situations that might cause panic, helplessness, or embarrassment -- Such phobics fear they will have a panic attack. They may fear wide-open spaces or crowded spaces.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adce", "question": "At which battle was poison gas first used?", "answer": "Second Battle of Ypres", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5f9", "question": "Coffee heiress Abigail Folger was one of the victims of which criminal?", "answer": "Charles Manson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c830", "question": "What hinged surfaces on a plane's wingtips allow the aircraft to roll?", "answer": "Ailerons", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b599", "question": "Which artist's song was the 10 billionth iTunes download?", "answer": "Johnny Cash", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd5", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"canyon\"?", "answer": "Spanish", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad26", "question": "Mehmat Ali Agca was accused of shooting whom in 1981?", "answer": "Pope John Paul II", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5feddfef6ce05a3942286db4", "question": "What do you call an object a person uses to ensure they are not in someone else's dream in the movie \"Inception\"?", "answer": "A totem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4de9e06d333868d34d718", "question": "The ancient Mayan civilization existed in which modern-day country?", "answer": "Guatemala", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e26", "question": "Who shares lead vocals with Bono on the U2 song \"When Loves Comes to Town\"?", "answer": "B.B. King", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c17f", "question": "What was George Hepplewhite's profession?", "answer": "Furniture maker", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59e8029ede59ea584496fe97", "question": "The song \"Hand on Your Heart\" was a hit in 1989 for which singer?", "answer": "Kylie Minogue", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd2d22a2596a59cbdfbd38b", "question": "Where is \"The Lush Valley of the Mills\"?", "answer": "Italy", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010c9af0775fa611bce67ee", "question": "What\u2019s the main difference between a bay and bow window?", "answer": "Number of sections -- Bay windows usually have three sections while bow windows have anywhere from four to six.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1bd", "question": "What year did Ferdinand Porsche and his team finish the design of the VW Beetle?", "answer": "1938", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a318", "question": "Which pop duo consisted of Fab Morvan and Rob Pilatus?", "answer": "Milli Vanilli", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a644", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the \"Buckeye State\"?", "answer": "Ohio", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59774321284458f1d7854425", "question": "Albert Einstein was offered the position of prime minister of what country?", "answer": "Israel", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2bd", "question": "How many seasons were there of the TV show \"30 Rock\"?", "answer": "7", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c837", "question": "What animal was used in British coal mines until being phased out in 1986?", "answer": "Canaries", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ffd", "question": "What British TV series featured James Hacker, MP, and Sir Humphrey Appleby?", "answer": "Yes, Minister", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aaba", "question": "What is the capital of Solomon Islands?", "answer": "Honiara", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa97", "question": "What ocean does the Zambezi River empty into?", "answer": "Indian ocean", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ed43db0d244b1771b64500c", "question": "In the end of the Netflix comedy film \"The Lovebirds\", which reality show do Jibran and Leilani compete on?", "answer": "The Amazing Race", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe771d1eec85e375820b300", "question": "Which country hosts the world's highest marathon?", "answer": "Nepal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339208", "question": "What pop star posed naked and pregnant on the August 2006 cover of Harper's Bazaar?", "answer": "Britney Spears", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "594d08381a1c922dd1ac64c1", "question": "Nordic and Alpine are two main genres of which sport?", "answer": "Skiing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1c9", "question": "What are the three primary ingredients in a standard Grasshopper cocktail?", "answer": "Creme de Menthe, Creme de Cacao and fresh cream", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c513", "question": "Which substance can you not eat, if you have celiac disease?", "answer": "Gluten", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf8a", "question": "A statue of Billy Bremner stands outside the ground of which football stadium?", "answer": "Leeds United", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398b7", "question": "In which movie does Clint Eastwood utter the line 'Go ahead, make my day\"?", "answer": "Sudden Impact", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fedda6a6ce05a3942286d85", "question": "What is Mr. Bean's actual first name?", "answer": "According to his television shows and movies, Mr. Bean's first name is actually \"Mr.\".", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a779", "question": "What body of water does the Colorado river empty into?", "answer": "The Gulf of California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c913", "question": "The amount of what substance in granite determines its color?", "answer": "Feldspar", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6015e427fe83fe1f2a824bae", "question": "The Battle of Kursk is best described as what type of battle?", "answer": "A tank battle", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5c2", "question": "Which two US states begin with the letter \"V\"?", "answer": "Vermont and Virginia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a119", "question": "Which classic Hollywood western is based on the film \"Seven Samurai\"?", "answer": "The Magnificent Seven", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c693", "question": "What do astronomers call an interstellar cloud of dust dust, hydrogen, helium and other ionized gases?", "answer": "Nebula", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aef1", "question": "When did The Black Death reach London?", "answer": "1348", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015e220fe83fe1f2a824b9c", "question": "What happened to the Soviet air force during the opening days of the German invasion?", "answer": "Up to 2000 aircraft were destroyed on the ground", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a85a", "question": "Which US state is the third largest state by land area?", "answer": "California", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ef3", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Henry Higgins?", "answer": "Pygmalion", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f29", "question": "Which band member of The Sex Pistols died of drug overdose?", "answer": "Sid Vicious", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "590722143745b36be73039fc", "question": "Who wrote the 1996 novel \"Certain Poor Shepherds: A Christmas Tale\"?", "answer": "Elizabeth Marshall Thomas", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393a7", "question": "In the movie \"Live And Let Die\", what ability does Solitaire lose after sleeping with Bond?", "answer": "Her psychic ability", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600b88bb1d8c1817608d53f6", "question": "What is New York City's largest store?", "answer": "Macy's -- The flagship Macy\u2019s in Manhattan\u2019s Herald Square covers an entire NYC block, with 2.2 million sq. ft. of retail space.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c34f", "question": "What shape is the body of an Erlenmeyer flask?", "answer": "Conical", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf4a", "question": "What is the last event in a decathlon?", "answer": "1500 Metres", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f6f", "question": "Who wrote the music to \"West Side Story\"?", "answer": "Leonard Bernstein", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b75", "question": "In \"Napoleon Dynamite\", what type of animal is Napoleon's grandmother's pet, Tina?", "answer": "llama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133942a", "question": "The 2007 movie \"There Will Be Blood\" is based on which novel by Upton Sinclair?", "answer": "Oil", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5ea", "question": "What designer introduced the miniskirt in 1965?", "answer": "Mary Quant", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b03e", "question": "What 1953 model of Chevrolet was first commemorated on a US postage stamp in 2005?", "answer": "The Corvette", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fa", "question": "What year did James Garfield start and end his presidency?", "answer": "1881", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a176", "question": "Who directed the film \"The Bridge on the River Kwai\"?", "answer": "David Lean", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c869", "question": "What tree's edible seeds were once used to weigh diamonds?", "answer": "The carob tree's", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff2587231a458464a93c466", "question": "Which type of pastry is traditionally boiled before it is baked?", "answer": "Bagel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a279", "question": "What was the birth name of actress Betty Grable?", "answer": "Elizabeth Ruth Grable", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fdabadc0b8cce1e6fda7058", "question": "Which country does the chorizo sausage originate from?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acd4", "question": "Who was Ronald Reagan's first wife?", "answer": "Jane Wyman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e5b", "question": "What literary work inspired Dream Theater's \"Pull Me Under\" song?", "answer": "Hamlet", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58c8a81990aac110e416708b", "question": "What name is shared between a 2nd Earl of Pembroke and an English cider?", "answer": "Strongbow", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8eb", "question": "Graphite dust is formed when what is cut with a laser?", "answer": "Diamond", "category": "science"}, {"id": "600398b657a0e35c43f8389d", "question": "James McNeill Whistler's Arrangement in Grey and Black No.1 is better known by what other name?", "answer": "Whistler's Mother\u00a0-- It is exhibited in the Mus\u00e9e d'Orsay in Paris, having been bought by the French state in 1891.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388fd", "question": "What nursery rhyme character was warned that the cow was in the corn?", "answer": "Little Boy Blue", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a311", "question": "Which 1970's sci-fi film featured a space ship named \"Nostromo\"?", "answer": "Alien", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c247", "question": "What is the term for the physical disintegration of a nuclear reactor's core?", "answer": "Meltdown", "category": "science"}, {"id": "60173d2b44491cbd7c5a17aa", "question": "What is the oldest active international airline?", "answer": "KLM Royal Dutch Airlines -- Founded in 1919, KLM is also the\u00a0oldest airline in the world\u00a0still operating under its original name.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59008f30cf842fa4c4ba96b9", "question": "Italian painter Jacopo Comin is better known as who?", "answer": "Tintoretto", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe773bceec85e375820b30c", "question": "How many \"emirates\" make up the United Arab Emirates?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd8d", "question": "What did Teleworld, Inc. rename itself in 1999, after its flagship product?", "answer": "TiVo", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e27", "question": "Who is Liza Minnelli's mother?", "answer": "Judy Garland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af16", "question": "Why were Julius and Ethel Rosenberg executed in 1953?", "answer": "Espionage", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b054", "question": "Who participated on the side of the Earp Brothers in the shootout at the OK Corral in 1881?", "answer": "\"Doc\" Holliday", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133947c", "question": "What was the last name of the family Seymour was stalking in the movie \"One Hour Photo\"?", "answer": "Yorkin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef5f566ce05a3942286e41", "question": "Who was the highest paid athlete of 2018?", "answer": "Floyd Mayweather", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acc0", "question": "What is the \"Big Mac\" that was built in Michigan in 1957?", "answer": "The Mackinac Bridge", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb52", "question": "What is the topmost part of a column called?", "answer": "Capital", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fde493ac6c6b019850c9a6d", "question": "Which Old Testament prophet said \"Thou art the man\"?", "answer": "Nathan", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe766b5eec85e375820b287", "question": "Captain Henry Morgan used what island as a base of buccaneer operations?", "answer": "Jamaica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fab", "question": "What novel was originally released under the title \"The Wild Palms\"?", "answer": "If I Forget Thee, Jerusalem", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe7cb7e877e98cb97778a1c", "question": "Which country's Easter brunch typically includes a ryemeal soup known as zurek?", "answer": "Poland", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd94", "question": "In 2002, Sony ended production of its recorders using what doomed video standard?", "answer": "Betamax", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e10", "question": "Philosopher Hannah Arendt's most famous book is named for what man \"in Jerusalem\"?", "answer": "Adolf Eichmann", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392ee", "question": "In the 1988 movie \"Die Hard\", what does John McClane leave in the limo?", "answer": "A teddy bear", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b50201dd7bf43be5e7cb", "question": "What is the main ingredient in the British dish laverbread?", "answer": "Seaweed", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338f35", "question": "Who titled his 1989 autobiography \"Holy Cow!\"?", "answer": "Harry Caray", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "597cdaa5e347d002c297e4d5", "question": "What nationality is Yehudi Menuhin?", "answer": "American", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afaa", "question": "St. Albans was the start and Bosworth field was the finish of what?", "answer": "War of the Roses", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6015fb83fe83fe1f2a824c39", "question": "St. Patrick wrote in his Declaration that when he was 16 years what happened?", "answer": "According to his own writings, St. Patrick said he was was captured by Irish pirates when he was 16 years old.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af0", "question": "Who was the first person to say the words \"Live from New York, it's Saturday Night!\"?", "answer": "Chevy Chase", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b605", "question": "Which impressionist featured his wife Camille, in \"The Woman in the Green Dress\"?", "answer": "Claude Monet", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cab4", "question": "What is the medical term for earwax?", "answer": "Cerumen", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c909", "question": "What name is given to animals which eat both plants and meat?", "answer": "Omnivore", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59e804aade59ea584496fea6", "question": "In which sport must the ball have a diameter of at least 42.67 millimetres and weigh no less than 45.93 grams?", "answer": "Golf", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6008dd5af4f3bc4a292f8620", "question": "During World War I and World War II, German submarines were called U-boats. What does \"U\" stand for?", "answer": "\"Unterseeboot\"-- It is German for undersea boat.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c062", "question": "Which Major League hitter drove in the most runs in a single season between 1980-89?", "answer": "Don Mattingly", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e44", "question": "What two-word phrase is the first writing to appear in \"Charlotte's Web\"?", "answer": "Some pig", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffe4b7b47818f5674af01b1", "question": "From which novel is this quote \"I\u2019m the most terrific liar you ever saw in your life. It\u2019s awful.\"?", "answer": "\"The Catcher in the Rye\" (The main character, Holden Caulfield, fittingly says this early in the novel while describing himself.)", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3bfaff048f679a45ab3a", "question": "What is the second largest animal in the world?", "answer": "Fin whale", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b01c", "question": "What U.S. President declared \"The ballot is stronger than the bullet\"?", "answer": "Abraham Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b4", "question": "In 1992, which US state began offering tourist info at 1-800-33-GUMBO?", "answer": "Louisiana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a78e20565ad31a57c7ea", "question": "Which US President was known as \"The American Cincinnatus\"?", "answer": "George Washington", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad7e95fb24f84e0b9f9ffcd", "question": "Seretse Khama was the first President of which African country?", "answer": "Botswana", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59a1a23212f2a7826b9b8719", "question": "Mel Gibson and Danny Glover appear in which series of films?", "answer": "Lethal Weapon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "592eaecdf83302ff91e4648d", "question": "Mark David Chapman became famous for what in 1980?", "answer": "Shooting John Lennon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "60062a58c9d816e292245c17", "question": "What is Judy Chicago's most well-known work?", "answer": "Regarded as the first epic feminist artwork, \"The Dinner Party\" functions as a symbolic history of women in Western civilization.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac2d", "question": "What started in 1849 when gold was discovered at Sutter's Mill?", "answer": "The California Gold Rush", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59675c4d2b59efe0e9417e94", "question": "What was Vince Gill\u2019s last #1 as a solo recording artist?", "answer": "Tryin\u2019 To Get over You", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c4a", "question": "According to poet Carl Sandburg, what \"creeps in on little cat feet\"?", "answer": "The fog", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f0", "question": "Who painted \"The Boy in the Red Vest\"?", "answer": "Paul C\u00e9zanne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3c9", "question": "The emperor penguin is the only type of penguin to inhabit which area?", "answer": "Antarctica", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b04e", "question": "Which U.S. President signed the National Aeronautics and Space Act establishing NASA?", "answer": "Dwight D. Eisenhower", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a9ec20565ad31a57c80d", "question": "The Nazi organization NSDAP stands for what?", "answer": "National German Workers' Party (Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterparteiz)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca07", "question": "The first integral of acceleration gives us what?", "answer": "Velocity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a950", "question": "What is the only US state with only one syllable?", "answer": "Maine", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6015e661fe83fe1f2a824bcc", "question": "Which king preceded Queen Victoria?", "answer": "King William IV (who was Victoria\u2019s uncle)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe657b5ae7e414034b5aee1", "question": "In the \"Book of Malachi\", God says that he has left the kingdom of Esau to which animals?", "answer": "Jackals", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a61", "question": "Whose wife could eat no lean?", "answer": "Jack Sprat", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5cd40ba5685cf15b733e988b", "question": "In which county in the United Kingdom is the Glastonbury Festival held?", "answer": "Somerset", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b092", "question": "When it was first created in 1938, what was the minimum federal wage in the US?", "answer": "25 cents per hour", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b916", "question": "What 2 letters in scrabble have the highest point value?", "answer": "Q and Z", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b188", "question": "Who succeeded Jimmy Carter as the 40th President of the United States?", "answer": "Ronald Reagan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff7c28f2b316f4693fb67a1", "question": "Which candy company is known as the primary producer of \"conversation hearts\" in the United States?", "answer": "The New England Confectionary Company or NECCO", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a47e", "question": "What is the capital of Vermont?", "answer": "Montpelier", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbe8", "question": "How many years did it take to build The Taj Mahal?", "answer": "22 years", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394a9", "question": "Who starred as John Drake in the TV show \"Secret Agent\"?", "answer": "Patrick McGoohan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c822fbde8045e48466d0", "question": "A medical condition that has been caused by a physician or medical treatment is described as what?", "answer": "Latrogenic", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba1f", "question": "In golf, what is the traditional name for a number 3 wood?", "answer": "Spoon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015e318fe83fe1f2a824ba6", "question": "During the Battle of Midway, Japan lost what?", "answer": "Most of its aircraft carriers.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c296", "question": "Who oversaw the design and assembly of the first atomic bomb?", "answer": "J. Robert Oppenheimer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5937edd308d98002fdd633cc", "question": "\"The Eroica\" is whose third symphony?", "answer": "Beethoven's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ffb666b5dad637d903c8836", "question": "Which English city was Alfred the Great's capital city?", "answer": "Winchester", "category": "geography"}]